doupto.com 2016-10-14

# Privacy Policy - DoUpTo

1\. Preface  
At DoUpTo Ltd. ("DoUpTo", "We" and "Us") user information is always kept private and secure. Our users can choose to remain anonymous even when paying or getting paid. DoUpTo provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of services, web site at: www.doupto.com ("the site"), feeds, features, content, applications or widgets, application program interfaces, application for third-party web sites and services, and any other web or mobile services or applications owned, controlled or offered by DoUpTo (collectively with the site: "The Service"). This privacy policy explains which information is collected by us when you use the service and how it is processed, used, protected and stored. We will not share your information with anyone, except as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means, including offline, or from other sources. We expect users to use the service strictly for harmless and legal uses. 

2\. What Personal Information We Collect?  
Personal Information You Provide to Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our Service or provide to us in any other way. The types of Personal Information collected may include your name, email address, phone number, birthday, Twitter and/or Facebook usernames, use information regarding your use of our Service, and browser information. We may also draw upon this Personal Information in order to adapt the Services of our community to your needs, to research the effectiveness of our network and Services, and to develop new tools for the community.   
Information Collected Automatically: When you use the Service, DoUpTo automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your location, IP address, cookie information, and the page you requested. We treat this data as non-Personal Information, except where we are required to do otherwise under applicable law. DoUpTo only uses this data in aggregate form.  
Information from other websites: We may institute programs with advertising partners and other websites in which they share information with us: (1) we may ask advertisers to tell us how our users responded to the ads we showed them (and for comparison purposes, how other users who didn't see the ads acted on their site). This data sharing, commonly known as "conversion tracking" helps us measure our advertising effectiveness and improve the quality of the advertisements you see. (2) We may receive information about whether or not you've seen or interacted with certain ads on other sites in order to measure the effectiveness of those ads. If we receive from the advertiser information we don’t already have, we will "anonimize" it for 180 days, meaning we will stop associating that information with any particular user. 

3\. How We Share Your Information?  
Personally identifiable information   
DoUpTo may share your personally identifiable information with third parties solely for the purpose of providing services to you. If we do this, such third parties’ use of your information will be bound by this Privacy Policy. We may store personal information in locations outside the direct control of DoUpTo (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers).  
DoUpTo does not share your personally identifiable information with other, third-party companies, for their commercial or marketing use without your express consent or unless you have opted-in to be part of a specific program or feature. We cannot control third parties’ use of your information. As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or dissolution.  
Sharing information in order to prevent harm and comply with the law   
Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, DoUpTo will not disclose personal information to any third party unless required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to:   
a) Conform to the law, comply with legal process served on us or our affiliates, or investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities.   
b) To enforce our Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, or to protect the security or integrity of our service.   
c) To exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of DoUpTo, our Users or others.  
d) We may respect requests to disclose information from jurisdictions outside Israel, if we have a good faith belief that the response is required by law under the local laws in that jurisdiction, apply to users from that jurisdiction, and are consistent with the generally accepted international standards.   
e) If we have a good faith belief it is needed to prevent fraud or other illegal activity or to prevent imminent bodily harm. 

**Non-personally identifiable information**  
We may share non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third parties to help them understand the usage patterns for certain DoUpTo services.   
In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of the service, DoUpTo often conducts research on its users demographics, interests and behavior based on personally identifiable information and other information that we have collected. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis and this aggregate information does not identify you personally and therefore is considered and treated as Non - Personally identifiable information under this Privacy Policy -. 

DoUpTo may also allow third-party ad servers or ad networks to serve advertisements on the DoUpTo Site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on DoUpTo. They automatically receive your IP address. when this happens, They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content. DoUpTo does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. However, please note that if an advertiser asks DoUpTo to show an advertisement to a certain audience and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. The DoUpTo Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, third-party advertisers. Please consult the respective privacy policies of such advertisers for more information.

4\. How We Protect Your Information?  
DoUpTo uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to DoUpTo and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, DoUpTo makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.  
To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you access to your account. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information, and for controlling access to your email communications from DoUpTo, at all times.  
Compromise of Personal Information  
In the event that personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, DoUpTo will promptly notify those persons whose personal information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy or as otherwise required by applicable law.  
Children’s Privacy  
Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important to us. For that reason, DoUpTo does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register as users. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information to or on DoUpTo. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under the age of 13, please contact us at here.

5\. Links to Other Web Sites  
We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website, nor the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link that leads from our website to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your use of any other website, including those that have a link on our website, is subject to that website’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

6\. Notification Procedures  
It is our policy to provide notifications, whether such notifications are required by law or are for DUTs, Seller/Buyer notifications, marketing or other business related purposes, to you via email notice, written or hard copy notice as determined by DoUpTo in its sole discretion. We reserve the right to determine the form and means of providing notifications to you.

7\. What about Cookies and Similar Technologies?  
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our site are visited and by how many people. DoUpTo cookies do not collect Personal Information, and we do not combine the general information collected through cookies with other Personal Information to tell us who you are or what your email address is.  
Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways.  
Ads appearing on the Service may be delivered to users by our advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by DoUpTo and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.   
8\. What about Log file information?   
Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you access a web page. When you register with or view our site, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include the following information: Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, your web request, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, device type, date and time, and other such information. The collection of this information may occur at: registration, login, and connecting to the server.  
9\. What we do with cookies and log file information?  
We use cookies and log file information to:   
1\. Remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the site.  
2\. Provide custom, personalized content and information.  
3\. Monitor the effectiveness of our Service.  
4\. Monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors and traffic.   
5\. Diagnose or fix technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with certain IP addresses.  
6\. Help you efficiently access your information after you sign in.

10\. What we do with e-mail information?   
By providing DoUpTo your e-mail address, you consent and agree to our using the e-mail address to send you DUTs, buyers/sellers notifications, service related notices, including any notices required by law, in lieu of communication by postal mail. We may also use your e-mail address to send you other messages, such as newsletters, changes to features of the service or to the Terms of Use, invitations to events and special offers.

11\. Monitoring Content  
DoUpTo reserves the right, but has no obligation, to monitor the Content and User Submission. We reserve the right to remove any such information or material for any reason or no reason, including without limitation if in our sole opinion such information or material violates, or may violate, any applicable law or our Terms of Use Agreement, or to protect or defend our rights or property or those of any third party. DoUpTo also reserves the right to remove information upon the request of any third party.

12\. Consent to collection and processing worldwide  
Please take note that by using DoUpTo you agree to have your personal data transported to and processed. You shall also take note that our server is located worldwide, and that your information may be stored everywhere. Before using the service you should take into account that any local applicable law may apply to your personal information. 

13\. Changes To This Privacy Policy  
This privacy policy may be updated from time to time. We will notify of any changes to this privacy policy by posting the new privacy policy on the site. In case there is a substantial change in the privacy policy, the change will not come into effect in the 7 days following its publication, during which you can reject the change by closing your account and discontinuing any use of the service. You are advised to consult this privacy policy regularly for any changes and / or updates.   
All the terms and conditions set forth in our [Terms of Use](http://doupto.com/terms-of-service "Terms of Service") apply to this privacy policy and you are advised to consult them. 

14\. What If I Have Questions Or Concerns?  
If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy using the Service, please contact us at here. [DoUpTo Contact Us](http://doupto.com/contact "DoUpTo Contact Us")

Last updated 14 August, 2011  
All subject to our Terms of Services
